Mandil Malla

Tama-Ku, shukugawara6-6-21lindesidekui103, Kawasaki

07085570709

mallamandilcoding@gmail.com

. =

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mandil-malla/

www.mandilmalla.me

As a highly motivated computer engineering graduate with a strong passion for technology, I possess over 6 months of experience in development using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for a company based in Nepal back in 2017. Additionally, I have gained valuable management skills through my experience in my previous work at a restaurant in Japan, where I also achieved JLPT N3 certification. Recently, I successfully completed Le Wagon's Web Development Bootcamp and have been dedicated to continuously enhancing my skills and staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends.

Personal Projects

Portfolio

- Different projects done through the skills I have learned and learning.
- Over 10+ projects
- Frontend html, css, js
- www.mandilmalla.me

Camera Equip

- Camera Rental web application
- Backend Ruby on Rails Frontend html, css, js, bootstrap Database: PostgreSql
- Website (login credentials: mallamandilcoding@gmail.com, 123123)

Travel Website clone

- Responsive website
- Frontend html, css, js, media queries
- Website

Quiz

- A quiz challenge based on the user preferences on what category s/he chooses with the help of trivia api
- Backend javascript Frontend html, css, javascript
- Website

ToDo List

- A todo list with crud operation using local storage to store/retrieve the data
- Backend javascript Frontend html, css, javascript
- Website

PHP crud

- A crud application done via PHP and Mysql as database with PDO.
- Backend Php Frontend html, css Datebase: Mysql
- Website

Techstack website clone

- A responsive website using react js library.
- Frontend html, scss, React js
- Website

Skills

Html5

Css3/ scss

- BootStrap
- Javascript
- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- SQL/Mysql

- PHP/Laravel
- Git
- React

Heroku/ Github pages/Netlify

Experience

JUN 2019 - JAN 2023

Sub Manager/Antworks Co. Ltd (Restaurant), Tokyo

- Managing stocks and shifts
- Guiding newcomers
- Handling kitchen/hall

DEC 2016 - JUN 2017

Programmer/ ABGS Group, Nepal

- Worked on making chat-bots for banks.
- Used php, html, css, js, mysql, git

Education

APRIL 2016

Bachelor in Computer Engineering/Advanced College of Engineering & Management, Nepal

Certifications

JAN 2023 - MAR 2023

Web Development/Le Wagon, Tokyo

FEB 2017 - MAY 2017

Front End Development/Halftone Design, Nepal

Languages

- English (Business)
- Nepali (Native)
- Japanese(N3)

Hindi (conversational)